ILGWU Southeast Region Records 5780/058
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Southeast Region Records
1937-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/058
48.5 cubic feet
48.5 linear ft.
Correspondence, agreements, records (documents).
Contains general chronological correspondence (1951-1966), weekly reports from organizers (1959-1960, 1972-1974), and alphabetical subject files. Among these alphabetical subject files are agreements (1946-1960), files on David Dubinsky (1947-1968), regional reports to the GEB (1947-1962), records of the regional office's political department (1948-1969), and material pertaining to the annual regional conference (1953-1969). Locals represented in the records of the Southeast Region include: 10, 23-25, 25, 62, 91 and 105 (New York, NY), 122 (Atlanta, GA), 375 (Birmingham, AL), 378 (Flagg-Utica), 457 (Cullman, AL), 473, and 574.
5491540
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
D. Mordente, October 13, 2008
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, June 19, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
Established in 1937, the Southeast Region of the ILGWU covered eight states: Alabama, Florida, Georgia, Louisiana, Mississippi, North Carolina, South Carolina, and Tennessee. John S. Martin served as director from the regional department's founding until his retirement in 1954. Elmer Kehrer succeeded him, holding the position until resignation in 1964. Martin Morand was director from 1964 to 1969, and after Morand's resignation, Nicholas Bonanno was appointed Director of the Southeast Region. Bonnano was still director of the region, at the time of the ILGWU's merger with ACTWU in 1995.
Scope and Contents
The collection is composed of a large number of records that can be described thematically by subject, including garment companies, regional and national departments, correspondence, and organizing.
A substantial amount of the records focuses on material pertaining to garment companies within the Southeast Region. These files often contain correspondence and reports, cases and complaints before the National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), NLRB agreements, grievances, affidavits, and awards from arbitration hearings. There is also information on the NLRB elections in various shops to determine whether the ILGWU would become the bargaining agent for employees, including ballots and results. Of particular interest to the researcher are the records documenting the difficulty the union had in organizing some of the shops, which often involved work stoppages and strikes. While there is much union literature that was passed out by organizers, also of research significance is the large number of anti-union flyers and correspondence as well as anti-union literature that was distributed by employers to their workers in an attempt to dissuade the employees from organizing.
The files of Alba-Waldensian, Inc. epitomize the type of material that can be found in the folders dedicated to the various garment companies. Alba-Waldensian, Inc. was a knitted outerwear producer that operated under the piece-rate system. When the company experienced losses in 1965, they reduced the piece rate, and the employees (not unionized) planned a strike. The ILGWU sent representatives to organize and the records document the subsequent conflict between union and management including correspondence, the U.S. Court of Appeals trial documents, exhibits, and evidence.
Some of the more notable companies with extensive files include: American Manufacturing Company; Appalachian Mills Company (Local 377, Knoxville, TN); Brunswick Manufacturing Company (Local 519, Brunswick, GA); Cherokee Sportswear, Inc. (Local 444, i.e. NLRB charges and agreements); Cullman Lingerie Corp. (Local 457, i.e. negotiations and grievance reports); E-Z Mills; Elberton Manufacturing Co. (Local 574, i.e. U.S. Court of Appeals and the piece rate system); Flagg-Utica Corporation (Local 378), G.C. Lingerie Corp. (Local 527); Garland Knitting Mills; Hartsville Manufacturing Co. (Local 515); Hobco Manufacturing Company; Jonathan Logan Inc. (Butte Knit Division); Judy Bond as well as its contractors and subsidiaries in its southern plants, including Brewton, AL (i.e. the "Don't Buy Judy Bond Blouses" campaign and the United Garment Workers of America); Levi Strauss Company (Local 516, i.e. withdrawals from the union); Marlene Industries Corp.; Movie Star, Inc. (Local 448); Palmetto Manufacturing Company (Local 122); and Signal Knitting Mills (Local 346).
A second component of the collection involves offices, departments and administrative material from the Southeast Region. Within the files of the Southeastern Regional office, there are listings of existing and new garment shops, correspondence and material on the annual Southeastern Region conference. While there is information on the many locals of the Southeast Region, unfortunately they are not delineated by local name or number, but instead, information on particular locals are found within the folders of the garment company of which that local was attached. For instance, the records of Local 457 would be within the files of the Cullman Lingerie Corp. Locals that do have their own folders include Local 122 Atlanta, which includes the constitution and by-laws, as well as the Miami Joint Council Cloak and Dress Makers' Union Locals 339 and 415.
Departments featured are the Political Department (political campaign contributions, campaign committees, and informational literature), the Legal Department (correspondence from the regional offices to those in the international legal department including General Counsel Morris Glushien; fees and expenses for various services and cases and contracts reviewed), the Union Label Department (correspondence regarding promotion and use of the label garments; the number of labels issued to firms in the region; union label kit for companies) and Unity Broadcasting Corporation and its attempt to secure FM radio licenses and stations across the region, including Chattanooga. There are also issues of the "Southern Garment Worker," the newsletter for the region.
Records on the Southeast Region Health and Welfare Fund include informational literature, correspondence, reports, Board of Trustees meetings and minutes, financial statements and contributions, as well as receipts and disbursements. Of particular interest is material on the Mobile Health Center Unit. The Mobile Health Center was a completely equipped diagnostic clinic on wheels which provided free annual examinations for ILGWU members throughout the Southeast. It was staffed by a physician, registered nurse, and laboratory technician. It was to travel from shop to shop in the Southeastern Region of the ILGWU. The records include the weekly reports and statistics such as the number of examinations performed and the routes taken between locals.
The ILGWU Training Institute began in 1950, graduating approximately 25 students annually. It was a full-time school for the training of union personnel which prepared individuals for careers in the ILGWU as organizers, representatives, administrators, technicians, and educators. The Southeast Region collection consists of correspondence, applicants, training material, listings showing the number of graduates on staff in the different regions, and especially graduates being sent to the Southeast Region for field training.
The Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR) was the attempt by staff members of the ILGWU to organize. FOUR was to be the exclusive bargaining representative for staff. The folders in this collection contain FOUR newsletters, letters to Dubinsky, articles, applications as well as withdrawals and resignations from FOUR, and the NLRB Case and subsequent balloting and voting for representation. Of special interest is the reaction to FOUR at the regional level, from the staff in the Southeastern Region offices.
Individuals with significant correspondence include Southeast Region Directors John S. Martin, E.T. Kehrer, Martin Morand, and Nick Bonanno, who started as an organizer in Mississippi, before moving to Tennessee as a business agent, and supervising the Carolinas, before becoming an assistant director of the Southeast Region, and finally a director. Other notable correspondence includes Harry Crone (Promotion Director ILGWU), Wilbur Daniels, David Dubinsky, Edward Kramer (Eastern-Out-Of-Town Department), Morris Glushien (General Counsel), Abraham Plotkin, Louis Stulberg, Gus Tyler and Frederick Umhey.
The final component of the collection focuses on the work of organizing the shops in the South. There is correspondence on organizing shops as the organizers themselves travel from city to city and factory to factory. The organizers stay in different hotels and locations on their journeys, and report back to the union on their progress. Included are the handwritten organizer's activity reports. These weekly reports are arranged by individual organizer and consist of forms to be filled out at the end of each week. The organizer reports chronicles their daily activities, filling out the name of the shop, type of work, what type of meeting took place (regular, special, executive board, committee, grievance), the number present at the meeting, and a listing of grievances and settlements. Other reports include places to list individuals met in the shops and indicate whether the visit resulted in a signed card, met with a refusal, person was out, or it was a repeat call. The work of the organizers are reflected in the collection through the documents on strikes and work stoppages, posters and leaflets passed out by the organizers, notices and memos to get employees to unionize, signing up members and union cards, and finally voting for union membership. The records help to illustrate the difficult task of organizing the shops in the South, as there is an abundance of anti-union literature and leaflets. The organizers were often met with disdain from employers, but also distrust from the workers too. The collection also contains literature on Right to Work laws for the states, many of which were in the South where the union was attempting to organize. Information on Right to Work includes pros and cons, employee views and how the laws impacted the worker, as well as complaints against compulsory unionism.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780/058 AV: ILGWU Southeast Region Audio Recordings
Women's clothing industry -- United States.; Labor unions -- Clothing workers -- United States.; Clothing workers -- United States.; Industrial relations -- United States.; Labor union--Organizing.; Southeast United States.; Bonanno, Nicholas.; Kehrer, Elmer T.; Martin, John S.; Morand, Martin.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. -- Southeast Region.
5491540
- Correspondence. Nick Bonnano., 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence. Nick Bonnano., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence. Nick Bonanno., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence and Misc. Notes. E.T. Kehrer, Morris P. Glushien., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence., 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence., 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Misc. Correspondence and Notes., 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence., 1959-1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Coed Collar Company. [folder 1 of 2], 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Coed Collar Company. [folder 2 of 2], 1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Complaints and Agreements. J.T. Flagg., 1946-1959 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Agreements and Correspondence., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Alabama Correspondence., 1947-1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- U.S. Court of Appeals. Alba-Waldensian, Inc., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Alba-Waldensian., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Alba-Waldensian. Trial Exhibits., 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Alba-Waldensian. Non-Evidentiary ULP Matters., 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Alba-Waldensian. ULP Evidence., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Alba-Waldensian. Misc., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Alba-Waldensian. Board Brief and Exceptions., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Alba-Waldensian. Trial File., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Alba-Waldensian. Motion to Correct Transcript., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Alba-Waldensian. Post-Hearing Matters. (including bargaining) [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Alba-Waldensian. Post-Hearing Matters. (including bargaining) [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Alba-Waldensian. Exceptions and Brief in Support., 1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Alba-Waldensian. TX Brief File No. 1., 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Alba-Waldensian. TX Brief File No. 2., 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Alba-Waldensian (USCA)., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Correspondence., 1947-1962 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- AFL Southern Campaign. Misc. [folder 1 of 2], 1942-1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- AFL Southern Campaign. Misc. [folder 2 of 2], 1942-1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- American Manufacturing Company. ULP Charges., 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- American Manufacturing Company. Case No. 15-RC-3199., 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- American Manufacturing Company. Misc., 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Appalachian Mills Company. Correspondence., 1950-1956 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Appalachian Mills Company. Misc., 1949-1952 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Correspondence., 1950-1955 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Correspondence. Kehrer., 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Athens Lingerie Corporation., 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Anthol Manufacturing Company., 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Atlanta Dress Manufacturers' Association., 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Atlanta Dress Manufacturers' Association. Arbitration and Correspondence., 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Auditor's Office. Correspondence., 1946-1960 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Auditor's Office. Correspondence and Misc., 1962 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Correspondence., 1957-1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Correspondence. Bach and Kehrer., 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Correspondence. Barker and Martin., 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Barnwell Garment Company., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Beauty Maid., 1957-1965 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Correspondence. Berger., 1957-1962 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Correspondence and Grievances. Misc., 1952-1962 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Bittmore Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Correspondence. Bishopville., 1953-1960 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Bobbie Brooks, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Bonnie-Frances Lingerie Company., 1957-1961 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Union Posters and Memos. [folder 1 of 2], 1954 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Union Posters and Memos. [folder 2 of 2], 1954 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Notices to Employees for Unionization., 1957 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Correspondence and Waivers., 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Correspondence., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Correspondence., 1949-1955 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Brunswick Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Brunswick Manufacturing Co., Inc. Misc., 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Brunswick Manufacturing Co., Inc. Agreement., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Brunswick Manufacturing Co., Inc. Misc., 1958-1965 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Butte Knitting Mills., 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Butte Knitting Mills. Correspondence., 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Correspondence., 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Correspondence., 1962-1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Correspondence and Grievance Reports., 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- CM Clothing. Correspondence., 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Calhoun Manufacturing Company., 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Federal Trade Commission. The California Sportswear and Dress Association., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Capital City Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1954-1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Carla Gay Dress Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1958 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Town of Leakesville v. Ruth Gettinger and State of Mississippi v. Ruth Staub., 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Cee Jay Manufacturing Co., 1966-1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Census and Records., 1951-1958 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- School for Workers., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Correspondence. Martin., 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Cherokee Sportswear, Inc. Misc., 1950-1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Cherokee Sportswear, Inc., 1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Cherokee Sportswear, Inc. Statements- RC and CA Cases., 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Cherokee Sportswear, Inc. Arbitration File., 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Cherokee Sportswear, Inc. Agreement., 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Cherokee Sportswear, Inc. Correspondence., 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Cherokee Sportswear, Inc. Ballots., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Cherokee Sportswear, Inc. Withdrawal Letters., 1966-1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Cherokee Sportswear, Inc. Election in Madisonville, TN., 1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Cherokee Sportswear, Inc. Contracts., 1967 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Child Care Centers., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Correspondence. Bialis and Kehrer, 1955-1962 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Clairmont Manufacturing, Inc., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Clinton Apparel Manufacturing Co., 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Coed Collar Co. [folder 1 of 3], 1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Coed Collar Co. [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Coed Collar Co. [folder 3 of 3], 1967 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Colebrook Knitting Mills, Inc. Discharge Arbitration., 1963-1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Colebrook Knitting Mills, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Colebrook Knitting Mills, Inc. Correspondence., 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Correspondence. Constangy and Kehrer., 1958-1962 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Correspondence. Constangy and Kehrer., 1946-1957 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Conventions., 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Correspondence. Cooper and Kehrer., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Cotton City Shops. [folder 1 of 2], 1957-1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Cotton City Shops. [folder 2 of 2], 1957-1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Correspondence. Crone., 1949-1959 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Croscill Curtain Co. and Durham Drapery Co., Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Croscill Curtain Co. and Durham Drapery Co., Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Cullman Lingerie Corp., 1949-1957 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Cullman Lingerie Corp., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Cullman Lingerie Corp., 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Cullman Lingerie Corp., 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Cullman Lingerie Corp., 1964-1969 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Correspondence. "D" Misc., 1957-1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Daisy's Originals, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Daisy's Originals, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Correspondence. Daniels., 1961-1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Debbie Dress, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Diamond Hoisery Corp., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Dino Boutiques, Inc., 1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Dixie Dress Co., 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Dorothy Lee, Inc., 1966-1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Drug Program, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Dubinsky, David., 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Dubinsky, David., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Dubinsky, David., 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Dubinsky, David., 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Dubinsky, David., 1962-1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Correspondence. Misc., 1954 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Correspondence. Dubinsky and Martin., 1947-1951 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Correspondence. Misc., 1951-1953 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Correspondence. Dubrow and Morand., 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Comparative Statement of Receipts. Dues Per Capita., 1943-1958 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Duncan Undergarment Company., 1957-1961 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Correspondence. Misc., 1939-1969 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- E-Z Mills, Inc. Arbitration., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- E-Z Mills, Inc. Unemployment Compensation Problem., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- E-Z Mills, Inc. [folder 1 of 3], 1966 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- E-Z Mills, Inc. [folder 2 of 3], 1966 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- E-Z Mills, Inc. [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- E-Z Mills, Inc. Campaign Literature., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- E-Z Mills, Inc. Bobbie Boston., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- E-Z Mills, Inc. Mary Lorene McIntire, Ruby McIntire., 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- E-Z Mills, Inc. Contract Negotiations., 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- E-Z Mills, Inc. Work Stoppage. [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- E-Z Mills, Inc. Work Stoppage. [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Correspondence. Kehrer and Kramer., 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Correspondence. Misc., 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company. [folder 1 of 4], 1964 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company. [folder 2 of 4], 1964 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company. [folder 3 of 4], 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company. [folder 4 of 4], 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company., 1959-1963 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company. Rhoda Lee Inc., 1963-1966 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company., 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company. Rhoda Lee- Piece Rate Problem at Elberton., 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company. Rhoda Lee Blouse Company Division., 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company. Rilla, Inc. and Rhoda Lee, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company. Negotiations., 1956-1967 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company., 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Elberton Manufacturing Company., 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Correspondence. Lokiec., 1965-1969 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Epstein-Harris Election., 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Evans Manufacturing Company., 1960-1965 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Exquisite Forms Industries., 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Exquisite Form Brassiere, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Exquisite Form Brassiere, Inc., 1954-1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Correspondence. F., 1959-1962 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Fairfield Manufacturing Company., 1962-1969 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Fairfield Manufacturing Company., 1956-1961 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Feature Manufacturing Company., 1960 (Box 22, Folder 6)